(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
惑星ループ
作詞・作曲：ナユタン星人
Planet Loop
Lyrics/Composition: Nayutalien
みんなー！4周年のミニライブ見に来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for coming to my 4th anniversary mini-live!
やったー！
Yay!
銀河の隅で 惑星はぐるぐる回る
In a corner of the galaxy, the planet goes round and round.
電波の記録 エコーが返ってきた これで何回だ
Records of radio waves, an echo returned. How many times is this now?
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
遠くの空で あなたに恋をしたんだ
In the distant sky, I fell in love with you.
届かないこと 分かってるのに
Even though I know it won't reach you.
あぁ あなたに会いたいな って気持ちがループ、ループする
Ah, the feeling of wanting to see you loops, loops around.
頭がどうにかなりそうだ それ以外考えられない
My head feels like it's going crazy. I can't think of anything else.
あぁ 今すぐ会いたいな って命がループ、ループする
Ah, I want to see you right now. My life loops, loops around.
この周回軌道上に あなたがいなくても
Even if you aren't on this orbit.
そこに大体 愛があるだけ
There's mostly just love there.
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
みんな、コメントありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for the comments!
声を辿って 乱反射で 延長線に消えてゆく
Tracing the voice, reflecting wildly, disappearing into the extension line.
このままパッと 忘れられたら 楽だろうな
It would be easier if I could just forget everything in an instant.
触れられないのに 見えてしまって どうしようもないや
I can't touch you, but I see you, and there's nothing I can do.
近くで遠い あなただ 分かってるよ
It's you, close yet far away. I know that.
あぁ それでも会いたいな って何度もループ、ループする
Ah, even so, I want to see you. It loops, loops over and over.
心があなたで鳴っている それだけが確かだ
My heart is ringing with thoughts of you. That's the only thing I'm sure of.
それだけでいいよ
That's all I need.
あぁ 星が回るように 僕らはずっとループ、ループする
Ah, just as the stars turn, we loop, loop forever.
想いが軌道を描いている あなただけを追うよ
My feelings are tracing an orbit. I'll chase only you.
あぁ 今すぐ会いたいな って命がループ、ループする
Ah, I want to see you right now. My life loops, loops around.
この周回軌道上に あなたがいなくても
Even if you aren't on this orbit.
それ以外思えない
I can't think of anything else.
そこに大体 愛があるだけ
There's mostly just love there.
みんな行くよー！
Here we go, everyone!
ハイ！
Hey!
そこに大体 愛があるだけ
There's mostly just love there.
はい！というわけで皆さんこんにちは、ときのそらです！
Yes! And so, hello everyone, I'm Tokino Sora!
お水もらった。
I got some water.
ミニライブ、会いに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to my mini live!
見て！久々に、あん肝も一緒に動いたよ！
Look! Ankimo is moving with me after a long time!
あん肝！
Ankimo!
あん肝も、歌いたいよー！
Ankimo wants to sing too!
イェーイ！
Yay!
やっぱ可愛い。可愛いけど...
He's cute after all. He's cute, but...
今日は、私が主役！
Today, I'm the main character!
あん肝デビュー、今日じゃないからね。
It's not Ankimo's debut today, okay?
と、いうわけで...
So...
久々にね、あん肝と私で、ちょっとね、お歌を歌うことができて、
After a long time, Ankimo and I could sing a bit together,
久々にこのステージに立つことができて、
And being able to stand on this stage again after so long,
とっても嬉しいです！
I'm very happy!
みんな！今日は盛り上がっていきましょう！
Everyone! Let's get excited today!
そして、そして、今日なんですが、今日なんですが、
And, and, as for today, as for today...
みんな、素敵なゲスト、呼んでるからね！
Everyone, I've called some wonderful guests!
早く、ゲストのみんなにも会いたいって思わない？
Don't you want to meet the guests soon?
思わない？
Don't you?
私は思います。
I do.
と、いうわけで、ここからはですね、
So, from here on...
ゲストのみんなと一緒に、お一人ずつね、デュエットとかやっていけたらいいなって思ってます。
I hope to perform duets with each of the guests, one by one.
それでは、まず、
Now then, first...
わためと一緒に、お歌を歌いたいと思います！
I'd like to sing a song together with Watame!
その曲は、こちら。
And the song is this one.
メランコリック！
Melancholic!
全然つかめない君のこと
You, whom I can't grasp at all
全然知らないうちにね
Before I even knew it
心奪われるなんてこと
That my heart would be stolen
あるはずないでしょう
There's no way that would happen, right?
わためー！
Watame-!
メランコリック 作詞・作曲：Junky
Melancholic. Lyrics & Composition: Junky
そらちゃん、おめでとう！
Sora-chan, congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
お邪魔します！
I'm joining in!
イェーイ！
Yay!
それは不愛想な笑顔だったり
Whether it's that unsociable smile
それは日曜日の日暮れだったり
Or the sunset on a Sunday
それはテストばっかの期間だったり
Or a period full of nothing but tests
それは君という名のメランコリーに誘われ
I'm lured by a melancholy called "you"
手当たり次第強気でぶつかっても
Even if I strike out at random with confidence
何も手には残らないって思い込んでる
I'm convinced nothing will remain in my hands
ちょっとくらいの勇気にだって
Even with just a little bit of courage
ちっちゃくなってふさぎ込んでる私だから
I'm the type to shrink back and mope
全然つかめない君のこと
You, whom I can't grasp at all
全然知らないうちにね
Before I even knew it
心奪われるなんてこと
That my heart would be stolen
あるはずないでしょう
There's no way that would happen, right?
全然気づかない君なんて
You, who doesn't notice at all
全然知らない、知らないもん
I don't know you, I don't care at all
ねぇねぇじゃないわ この笑顔
It's not "hey hey", this smile
また眠れないでしょう
I probably won't be able to sleep again
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
イェーイ！
Yay!
明日も同じ私がいるのかな
I wonder if the same me will be there tomorrow
不愛想で無口なままの可愛くないやつ
An uncute person, remaining unsociable and silent
あぁ...
Ah...
あの夢に君が出てきたときから
From the time you appeared in that dream
素直じゃないの だって
I'm not being honest, because...
全然つかめない君のこと
You, whom I can't grasp at all
全然知らないうちにね
Before I even knew it
心奪われてたのは
The one whose heart was stolen...
私の方だもん
...was me
るららるらら...
Lulala lulala...
足りない　私のメランコリック
Not enough of my melancholic
イェーイ！
Yay!
おめでとう！ ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thank you for inviting me!
こちらこそありがとう！
No, thank you as well!
はい！というわけで1人目のゲストは...
Okay! So, the first guest is...
角巻わため！ わためだー！
Tsunomaki Watame! It's Watame!
お邪魔します！ よろしくお願いします！
Thanks for having me! Nice to meet you!
せーの！ ドドド、ドドドド、ドドド、ドドドド...
Ready, go! Dododo, dododo, dododo, dododo...
こんばんドドド！ ドドドドドド！
Konban-dododo! Dodododododo!
いや、最後のところさ...
So, at the end...
ハート、1人でやってたから...
You were doing the heart by yourself...
ちょっと待って、一緒にやってたよ！
Wait a minute, I was doing it with you!
えっ、ホント？ やったよ！
Eh, really? I did it!
あ、やってくれた？ うん、やろ。
Oh, you did? Yeah, let's do it.
届かないけど。
We can't reach, though.
いやー、来てくれてありがとう。
Anyway, thanks for coming.
いや、こちらこそ呼んでくれてありがとう！
No, thank you for inviting me!
なんかね、せっかくの4周年だから、誰かと一緒に歌いたいなと思って。
Since it's my 4th anniversary, I wanted to sing with someone.
うわあ、嬉しい、呼んでくれて。
Wow, I'm so happy you invited me.
ね。今度はあれもやろうね、ゲームも。
Right. Let's play that game next time too.
ゲーム？ あ、あれ？ 探索？
Game? Oh, that? Exploration?
そう、探索ね！ そう！
Yeah, exploration! Yes!
さっきね、そう、それも、待ってる間に...
Just before, yeah, while we were waiting...
「あ、わため今度さ」って言おうとしたら...
I was about to say, "Hey Watame, next time..."
同じ、同じタイミングでね。
At the same, same time.
そう。探索、あ！みたいな。
Yeah. Exploration! Ah! Like that.
「あ、同じこと言おうとしてた」って。
We said, "Oh, we were about to say the same thing."
おおーってなって。心がね、通じ合ってるのがね、わかりました。
We were like "Oh!" and I felt our hearts were connected.
通じ合っちゃったんですね。 ね。
Our hearts were connected. Right.
今回ね、メランコリックを一緒に歌ってもらったんですけど...
We sang 'Melancholic' together this time...
このメランコリックは、なんか私も結構初期の頃に歌わせていただいてる曲で...
'Melancholic' is a song I sang back in my early days...
で、わためもね、素敵なアレンジで歌っていたのも見ていたので...
And I saw Watame singing it with a great arrangement...
こう、一緒に歌えたら嬉しいなと思って選んだんだ。
So I chose it because I thought it would be nice to sing together.
嬉しいです！
I'm so happy!
そらちゃんの歌ってみたも聴いてるよ。
I've listened to your cover too, Sora-chan.
ホントに？
Really?
うん。
Yeah.
な、恥ずかしいな...
I'm embarrassed...
いやもう、前から、ずっとわためと一緒に歌いたくて。
I've wanted to sing with Watame for a long time.
歌いたかったー！
I wanted to sing too!
憧れの先輩だで。
You're the senior I look up to.
緊張したで。
I was nervous.
憧れって思われて、わあ、ちょっとびっくりしちゃった。
I was surprised to hear I'm someone you look up to.
緊張してる？
Are you nervous?
ホントに？さっきあんなに走り回ってたのに。
Really? Even though you were running around earlier?
ドキドキだったよ！
My heart was pounding!
ホント？
Really?
でもリハーサルでもね、二人ですごい何度もやったもんね。
But we practiced together so many times in rehearsal, didn't we?
やった。ギリギリまでやった。
We did. Right up until the last minute.
そう。ギリギリまでね。
Yeah. Until the very last minute.
「はい、あともう1回、もう1回」って言ってね。
We kept saying, "One more time, one more time."
歌えましたね。
We were able to sing it.
ねえ、こちらこそありがとうございます。
Right, thank you as well.
はい、そらさんの。
Yes, Sora-san's...
また、今度、一緒に歌ってくれますか？
Um, would you sing with me again sometime?
もちろん！
Of course!
やったー！
Yay!
これでね、こちらこそお願いします。
With this... I should be the one asking. Please.
やめてよ、やめてよ！
Stop it, stop it!
お願いします。
Please.
いや、こちらこそ本当に。あ、いいんですよ、すみませんなんか。
No, really, me too. Oh, it's okay, I'm sorry.
なんてこと... これが「床」か。
Oh my... so this is what it means to be on the floor.
床になっちゃったね。
We ended up on the floor.
床になる、はまたね、別の...
To "become the floor" is a different thing...
別の。
In another way.
今笑ってますけども。
I'm laughing now, though.
どこかでニヤニヤしてますけども。
I'm grinning somewhere inside.
というわけで、まだまだゲストはいるので...
Anyway, there are still more guests...
次のゲストさんに行こうかなと思います！
So I think I'll move on to the next guest!
わため、ありがとう！
Watame, thank you!
また後でね！
See you later!
後でね！
後でねー！
See you!
はい、というわけで、次の曲に行きましょう。
Okay, so let's move on to the next song.
次は、星街すいせいちゃんと、「打上花火」。
Next is 'Uchiage Hanabi' with Hoshimachi Suisei-chan.
あの日見渡した渚を　今も思い出すんだ
I still remember the shore I looked out over that day
砂の上に刻んだ言葉　君の後ろ姿
The words carved in the sand, your silhouette from behind
寄り返す波が　足元をよぎり何かをさらう
The returning waves brush my feet and wash something away
夕凪の中　日暮れだけが通り過ぎて行く
In the evening calm, only the sunset passes by
...てゆく
...flowing away.
パッと光って咲いた
Blooming with a sudden flash,
花火を見ていた
we were watching the fireworks.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely, the summer that's not over yet...
曖昧な心を
...thawed and connected...
解かして繋いだ
...our ambiguous hearts.
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to continue.
あと何度君と同じ花火を見られるかなって
I wonder how many more times I can see
the same fireworks with you.
笑う顔に何ができるだろうか
What can I do for that smiling face?
傷つくこと 喜ぶこと 繰り返す波と
Getting hurt, being happy, the repeating waves...
ちょうど 焦燥 最終列車の音
...just then, impatience, the sound of the last train.
何度でも言葉にして君を呼ぶよ
I'll put it into words and call you
over and over.
波間を選び もう一度
Choosing the gaps between waves, once more.
もう二度と 悲しまずに済むように
So that we never have to be sad again.
ハッと息を飲めば 消えちゃいそうな光が
If I catch my breath, the light that
seems ready to fade...
きっとまだ 胸に住んでいた
...was surely still living in my heart.
手を伸ばせば触れた あったかい未来は
The warm future I could touch if I reached out...
ひそかに二人を見ていた
...was secretly watching the two of us.
パッと花火が
Suddenly, the fireworks...
夜に咲いた
...bloomed in the night.
夜に咲いて
Blooming in the night,
夜に咲いた
they bloomed in the night.
静かに消えた
They quietly disappeared.
離さないで
Don't let go.
離れないで
Don't leave.
もう少しだけ
Just a little longer.
このままで
...as we are.
あの日見渡した渚を 今も思い出すんだ
I still remember the beach we looked
out over that day.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉 君の後ろ姿
The words carved in the sand, the sight of your back.
パッと光って咲いた
Blooming with a sudden flash,
花火を見ていた
we were watching the fireworks.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely, the summer that's not over yet...
曖昧な心を
...thawed and connected...
解かして繋いだ
...our ambiguous hearts.
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to continue.
はい！ということで！
Yes! So!
2人目のゲストは、すいちゃーん！
Our second guest is Suichan!
はーい！星街すいせいでーす！皆さんこんにちは、お邪魔します。
Hello! It's Hoshimachi Suisei! Hello everyone, thanks for having me.
そらちゃん、おめでとう！
Sora-chan, congratulations!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
届かない！
I can't reach!
すいちゃんはー？
What about Suichan?
今日も可愛いー！
Still cute today!
そらちゃんはー？
What about Sora-chan?
今日も可愛いー！
Still cute today!
ありがとー。
Thank you.
気恥ずかしくなっちゃった。
That's getting a bit embarrassing.
そらちゃんとね、久しぶりに歌いましたね、一緒に。
It's been a while since I sang with Sora-chan like this, hasn't it?
ね。いつぶりだろうか。
Yeah. I wonder how long it's been.
いつぶりかな？
I wonder when.
すいちゃんのライブにゲストで出た時？
Was it when I was a guest at your concert, Suichan?
あん時かな、やっぱ最後。1年ぶりくらい？
That might have been the last time. About a year ago?
なんかそんな気がする。
I think so too.
割と、えっと、1年...
It was quite, well, a year...
うん。そんなに一緒にやってないのか。
Yeah. We haven't done it together that much.
いやでも今日ね、呼んでくれて本当に嬉しかった。
But I was really happy you invited me today.
いや私も来てくれて本当に嬉し...
No, I was really happy you came...
ねぇ、めちゃくちゃ難しい曲だから、めちゃくちゃね、練習したんだけど。
It's a really difficult song, so we practiced a lot.
そう！
Yes!
すごいね、2人でリハもね、「ここ、こうする？」とか。
Right, during rehearsal we were like, "Should we do this here?"
「ハモる？」とか話ししてたんだけど。
Or "Should we harmonize?"
ちょっとこれはそらちゃんの声を活かしたいなと思って私は何もしませんでした。
But I thought I wanted to make the most of Sora-chan's voice, so I didn't do anything extra.
うふふ、入れて？
Hehe, you put it in?
嬉しいなと思って来ました
I'm so happy to be here.
いつでもあんのかな、ここは
I wonder if it's always like this here.
水がね、ひたひたで
The water is all over the place.
滑っちゃうな、それは。滑っちゃうな、それは
You'll slip like that. Yeah, you'll slip.
かなり聞いてる。かなり聞いてるって。何を？
I've heard it a lot. Heard what?
お、何を？あ、そう、まあでも
Oh, what? Ah, right, well...
我々二人で歌ってみた動画を出してはいるんですよ
The two of us did release a cover video together.
それをいっぱい聴いてくれてるのかな？
I wonder if everyone's been listening to it a lot?
ぜひ聴いてください、たくさん。聴いてください
Please listen to it many times. Please do!
お願いします。そん時は私がそらちゃん誘ったんだけど
Please. Last time, I was the one who invited Sora-chan.
今回はなんとそらちゃんから誘っていただきまして
But this time, Sora-chan was the one who invited me.
あー、嬉しいなと思いながら今日は来ました
I'm so happy to be here today.
いや、すごいね、すごく快諾して。嘘、嘘、嘘
Yeah, you agreed immediately. No way!
あの、これやりたいんだけどスケジュール教えて、みたいな
"I want to do this, tell me your schedule," she said.
そう、あ、スケジュール次第で全然行けますけど、みたいな
And I was like, "I'm totally free depending on the schedule."
もうすごいあっさり来るじゃんと思って
I thought, "Wow, she's so casual about it."
そう、やります！って。大体すいちゃんそうだから
"I'll do it!" Suisei is usually like that.
何かやる？やる！みたいな
"Wanna do something?" "Yes!"
ノリがめちゃくちゃいいじゃん。そう、やるって
You have such a great vibe. Yeah, let's do it!
今日も軽率な持ち味で、やる！って来ました
Today too, with my usual lightheartedness, I came here saying "I'll do it!"
いやでも、そういう気持ちで来てくれるのが一番嬉しい
But honestly, that enthusiasm makes me the happiest.
すごく楽しかった。やっぱそらちゃんと一緒に歌えるっていうのは
It was so much fun. Getting to sing with Sora-chan...
我々からしたらもうビッグイベントですからね
...is a huge event for us.
ビッグイベントですからね。ほんとに？
A huge event! Really?
そうだよ、そうだよ。なかなかないことですからね。確かにね
That's right. It doesn't happen very often. True.
もう4年ですよ、そらちゃん。もう4年
It's already been 4 years, Sora-chan. 4 years already.
すいちゃんもだから割と...あ
Suisei, you've also been around for a while...
そう、割とでも近いよね。近いよね
Yeah, our timing is actually quite close. It is.
私が来年の3月で4年だから。そうだよね
My 4th anniversary will be next March. That's right.
そう、半年ないくらいな差かな。半年差
So there's less than a six-month difference.
あ、半年差か、ぐらい。
About a six-month gap, then.
いやでもさ、そんなに経った感じする？
But does it feel like that much time has passed?
しない。しない。しない、全く。全然しないよね
No. Not at all. It doesn't feel like it at all.
そうなんだよ。みんなもさ、そうじゃない？
Exactly. I bet it's the same for everyone else too.
あんまりそんなに経った感じないよね、きっと。うん
It probably doesn't feel like that much time has passed.
そうかも。初期からね、追ってるそらとものみんなは
Maybe. For the Soratomos who've been following since the start...
もう4年か、って。そんなに経ったんだ、って
...they must be thinking, "It's already been 4 years?"
みんなあれじゃない？月日の速さにびっくりしちゃってんじゃなかろうか
Everyone's probably surprised by how fast time flies.
そうかもね。いやでもさ、
Maybe. But you know...
やっぱ4年前の一番最初の頃と比べて、今はこんな大きなステージに
...compared to 4 years ago, being on such a big stage now...
環境とかはすごい変わってるけど。うん。
The environment has changed a lot, hasn't it?
なんていうの、もう考え方とか大して変わってないんだよね
But my way of thinking hasn't really changed much.
そっかそっか。なんかね、ずっとずっと、こんな感じで
I see. You've always been like this.
のらりくらりと。このままね、
Just taking it easy. And like this...
10年、20年と続けていければいいなと思うね。うん
I hope to continue for another 10 or 20 years.
これからも頑張っていただきたい、そらちゃんには
I want Sora-chan to keep doing her best.
いや、すいちゃんもでしょ。私ももちろん頑張りますけれども
You too, Suisei! Of course, I'll do my best too.
これからも、5年目も6年目も7年目も8年目も
From now on, for the 5th, 6th, 7th, 8th year...
めっちゃ噛んでる。9年目もずっとずっと頑張っていってください
You're stumbling over your words! And for the 9th year too...
頑張ります。お互い頑張ろう。うん、頑張ろう
I will! Let's both do our best! Yeah!
先輩！先輩！
Senpai! Senpai!
というわけで、2人目のゲスト、星街すいせいちゃんでした！
So, our second guest was Hoshimachi Suisei-chan!
イエーイ！またねー！
Yay! See you later!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
では、次に行きたいんですが、一回お水を飲みます
I'd like to move on to the next part, but first, a water break.
はい、というわけで、次はAZKiと一緒に歌を歌っていきます
All right, next I'll be singing a song with AZKi.
それも2人で歌うのは初めての曲です
This is also a song we've never sung together before.
only my railgun！
only my railgun!
一緒に歌おう！行くぞ！
Let's sing together! Let's go!
放て! 心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえ置き去りにして
Release it! The dream carved in my heart, leaving even the future behind
限界など知らない 意味無い! この力が光散らす
I don't know any limits, it's meaningless! This power scatters light
その先に遥かな想いを
Beyond that, distant feelings
歩いてきた この道を
Having walked this path
振り返ることしか
If I can only look back
できないなら 今ここで
If I can't do anything else, then right here
全てを壊せる
I can destroy everything
暗闇に落ちる街並み
Streets falling into darkness
人はどこまで立ち向かえるの?
How far can people stand up to it?
加速するその痛みから
From that accelerating pain
誰かをきっと守れるよ
I can surely protect someone
Looking the blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my railgun can shoot it. 今すぐ
Only my railgun can shoot it. Right now
身体中を 光の速さで駆け巡った 確かな予感
A sure premonition that coursed through my body at the speed of light
掴め! 望むものなら残さず 輝ける自分らしさで
Seize it! If it's what you want, leave nothing behind with your own shining self
信じてるよ あの日の誓いを この瞳に光る涙
I believe in that day's vow, the tears shining in these eyes
それさえも強さになるから
Even that will become strength
立ち止まると少しだけ感じる切なさに
In the brief sadness I feel when I stand still
戸惑うことないなんて嘘はつかないよ
I won't lie and say I'm never confused
空に舞うコインが描く放物線が決める運命
The fate decided by the parabola drawn by a coin dancing in the sky
打ち出した答えが今日も私の胸を駆け巡る
The answer I shot out still races through my chest today
Sparking! The shiny lights awake true desire Only my railgun can shoot it 今すぐ
Sparking! The shiny lights awake true desire. Only my railgun can shoot it, right now
貫いてく戸惑うことなく傷ついても走り続ける
Piercing through without confusion, I'll keep running even if I get hurt
Believe in it 煌めく視線は狂いなく闇を切り裂く
Believe in it, my sparkling gaze cuts through the darkness without straying
迷いなんて吹き飛ばせばいいこの心が叫ぶ限り
Just blow away any hesitation, as long as this heart is screaming
誰一人邪魔などさせない
I won't let anyone get in the way
儚く舞う数多の願いはこの両手に積もっていく
Countless fleeting wishes pile up in these hands
切り裂く闇に見えてくるのは重く深く切ない記憶
What I see in the darkness I cut through are heavy, deep, and painful memories
色褪せてく現実に揺れる絶望には負けたくない
I don't want to lose to the despair swaying in the fading reality
私がいま私であること胸を張って全て誇れる
I can proudly take pride in everything about who I am now
Looking for the special radiance that stays Only my railgun can shoot it 今すぐ
Looking for the special radiance that stays. Only my railgun can shoot it, right now
体中を光の速さで駆け巡った確かな予感
The definite premonition that raced through my body at the speed of light
放て！心に刻んだ夢を未来さえ置き去りにして
Fire! Leaving even the future behind, the dream carved in my heart
限界など知らない意味ないこの力が光散らす
Meaningless to know limits, this power scatters light
その先に遥かな想いを
Sending my distant thoughts beyond that
そらちゃーん！
Sora-chan!
あずきちー！
AZKi-chi!
すごい緊張してた。
I was so nervous.
改めて4周年おめでとう！
Once again, happy 4th anniversary!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
もう4周年かー。いや、すごい、本当に本当に。
Has it been 4 years already? Wow, amazing, really, really.
5年目か。5年目のそらちゃん。
The 5th year. Sora-chan in her 5th year.
そうだよ、もう5年目だよ。
That's right, it's already the 5th year.
5年目のそらちゃん。めちゃくちゃ大先輩だ。
Sora-chan in her 5th year. She's a huge senior.
5歳だ。
I'm 5 years old.
5歳だ。そうやって言うと、一気に子供みたいな。
5 years old. When you put it like that, you suddenly sound like a kid.
5歳になりましたーって。
I've turned 5 years old!
今日は呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thank you for inviting me today!
とても嬉しい。なんかこんな素敵な、なんだ、ライブで、SorAZで今日歌えるなんて。
I'm so happy. To be able to sing as SorAZ today in such a wonderful live concert...
めちゃくちゃ嬉しくて、嬉しくて、嬉しくて。
I'm just so, so, so happy.
イェーイ！
Yay!
いや、あずきちともね。もう結構長いよね。
Well, it's been quite a long time with AZKi-chi too.
ね、そうだよね。もう何年、何年だろう。
Yeah, that's true. How many, how many years has it been?
最初になんかSorAZでライブしたのが、でもなんか昨日のことのように。
The first time we did a SorAZ live feels like it was just yesterday.
でも、もう3年前とかじゃない？
But wasn't it like 3 years ago?
だよね。そうだよ、きっと。
Right. Yeah, it must be.
そんな、そう。最初ね、だから最初さ...
Yeah. At first, you know, at first...
なんか「そら先輩」って呼んでて。
I used to call you "Sora-senpai".
今では考えられない！
Unthinkable now!
考えられない。今「そら先輩」って言われたら「えっ」ってなっちゃう。
Unthinkable. If I were called "Sora-senpai" now, I'd be like, "Huh?"
そう、そら先輩って呼んでて、で、なんか...
Yeah, I called you Sora-senpai, and then...
そらちゃんが、なんか「そらちゃんって呼んで」っていうのを、そのライブで多分言ってくれて。
Sora-chan probably told me to call her "Sora-chan" during that live.
あ、そうだ。ライブで言ったんだっけ？
Oh, that's right. Did I say that at the live?
そうそうそう。そっか。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I see.
それすら記憶に...
Even that's not in my memory...
当たり前かのように「そらちゃん」って呼んでいますけれども、そんなそんなこともあったなと思って。
I call you "Sora-chan" as if it's the most natural thing now, but I was thinking how there was a time like that.
そっからいろいろね、一緒にほら歌ってみたとかね。
From there, we did various things together, like song covers.
確かに。
True.
意外とだから、いっぱいいろんな歌歌ってるんだけど。
So, surprisingly, we've sung many different songs.
そうなんだ、そうなんだ。今回のこの曲は、
That's right, that's right. This song this time...
あ、そう。この選曲は、そらちゃんが聞きたかった。
Oh, right. As for this song choice, I wanted to hear it, Sora-chan.
なんか一緒に歌いたいなってなったときに、
When I felt like I wanted to sing together...
どうせだったら二人で歌ったことがない曲と思って、で考えてたの。
I thought I'd choose a song we've never sung together, so I was thinking about it.
で、実は、そのときにあずきちの歌とかを全部聴いてて。
And actually, at that time, I was listening to all of AZKi-chi's songs.
で、そう、リストとかと照らし合わせて。
And yeah, comparing them with the list.
そのときに「only my railgun」を歌ってる...これ結構前だよね、これも。
At that time, I saw you singing "only my railgun"... This was quite a while ago too, right?
そうだね、だいぶ前かもしれない。
Yeah, it might have been a long time ago.
のを見て「あ、かっこいい。あ、これだ」って。
I saw that and thought, "Oh, cool. This is it!"
これで、これ二人で歌いたいってなって...
With this, I decided I wanted to sing this as a duo...
ねえ、やっぱ難しいじゃん、やっぱこの曲って。
Right? This song is really difficult, after all.
ねえ、そうだよね、難しいよね。
Yeah, it is, isn't it? It's difficult.
大丈夫かなって思ったら、なんか二人の声で、あ、全然大丈夫ってなって。
I was worried if it'd be okay, but when I heard our voices together, I was like, "Oh, it's totally fine!"
流石！
As expected!
でもでも、だから、そらちゃんが歌いたいって、なんかその、そらちゃんが歌ってるところを、なんか聞いたことなかったからめっちゃ...
But, but, so, when you said you wanted to sing it, Sora-chan... since I hadn't heard you singing this part before, I was really...
あー、あんまり歌ってないからね。
Ah, I don't sing it much, after all.
めっちゃ新鮮。いいのかな、いいのかな、そんなそらちゃん見れちゃって、いいのかなって思って。
It's so fresh. I was like, "Is it okay? Is it really okay for me to see Sora-chan like this?"
いやいやいや、今日楽しみにしてきた。
No no no, I've been looking forward to today.
いや、そうなんだよ、そうなんだよ。
Yeah, that's right, that's right.
だからね、本当になんかこう、なんか自分がやりたいことを、みんなに叶えてもらってるからね、本当に。
So really, everyone is making my wishes come true today, seriously.
ねえ、今日詰め込んだね、そらちゃんの、そう、すごいね。
You really packed it in today, Sora-chan. It's amazing.
今日ね、ゲストもそうだし...
Today, the guests too...
もう選曲もそうだし、やりたいことすごいやってるから。
The setlist too. I'm doing so many things I wanted to do.
まだやれてないことあるんじゃないですか？
Isn't there still something you haven't done yet?
あります！
There is!
というわけで！
And so!
ということで！
That means!
二人来てよー！すいちゃん、わためぇ！
Come on out, you two! Sui-chan, Watame!
何？この動き。
What's this movement?
急に直立。
Suddenly standing upright.
ここ、ここ！
Here, here!
ここです！ここです！
It's here! It's here!
立ち位置！立ち位置です、四人の立ち位置。
The positions! These are our standing positions. Our positions for the four of us.
すごい、って、揺れてる。めちゃくちゃ揺れてる。
Wow... Wait, you're swaying. You're swaying a lot.
何やってるん？
What are you doing?
イエーイ！
Yay!
というわけでね、私がね、やりたいもう一つのことっていうのが、私の曲を四人で歌いたいな、みたいな。
So, another thing I want to do is to sing one of my songs with the four of us.
いいよ！歌おう！レッツゴー！
Sure! Let's sing! Let's go!
やったー！そう、なんかね、私の曲は、誰に聞いても「高い」「高い」「きつい」って言われるんですけど...
Yay! Yeah, you know, no matter who I ask about my songs, they always say they're "high," "high," and "tough," but...
高い、高い、きつい！
High, high, tough!
でも、歌います！
But we're going to sing!
なんですけど、歌ってくれるということで。まあね、私の名前が、あの、曲の中に出てくる曲なので...
Since they agreed to sing it with me... Well, it's a song where my name appears in the lyrics...
なんと！あれじゃねえか！あれじゃねえか！
What! Could it be that one?! It must be that one!
ということで、みんなで歌っていきたいと思いますので、よろしくお願いします！
So, we'd like to sing it all together. Here we go!
それでは行きます！Dream☆Story！
Here we go! Dream Story!
せーの、いくよー！
Ready, set, go!
ふと忘れてしまいたくなる　昨日のあの記憶のピース
Sometimes I want to just forget those pieces of yesterday's memories
無くしたりはできそうもないけど　上手く繋げばまた続きへ
I don't think I can lose them, but if I connect them well, they'll lead to what's next
でも今は関係ないんだよ　そんなことも忘れちゃうような
But it doesn't matter right now. Something that'll make me forget all that...
不思議な世界にアクセル全開で　飛び込もう　It's Show Time!
Let's dive into a mysterious world with full throttle! It's Show Time!
でもでも急ぎ足は禁物です　急がば回ってるってくらいじゃん
But, but, rushing is forbidden. It's like "haste makes waste."
だからたまにはゆっくり一休みしたら
So once in a while, let's take a slow break, and then...
それじゃちょい早めのリズムで
Then, with a slightly faster rhythm...
みんな行くよー！
Everyone, here we go!
止まらねぇぞー！
Don't stop!
飛んでけハイ　大きく深呼吸したら僕らの　ストーリーが今　溢れ出すよ
Fly high! After taking a deep breath, our story starts to overflow now
もっともっと大きくね！
Even bigger, bigger!
最初が肝心なんです
The beginning is what's important
はじめましてこんにちは　せーの！
Nice to meet you, hello! One, two!
ときのそらだよ！
I'm Tokino Sora!
舞い踊れバイ　空遠くまで届けドキドキで
Dance on by! Let the heartbeat reach far into the sky
そう世界彩ってくドリームストーリー　やっぱ一秒たりとも目を離さないでほしいな
Yeah, the Dream Story that colors the world. After all, I don't want you to look away for even a single second
まばたきもしてらんない！
You can't even blink!
あーほらね最高でしょ？
Ah, see? It's the best, right?
イエーイ！
Yay!
一歩進めばまた白へ　見えない力が邪魔している
Take one step and it's back to white. An invisible force is getting in the way
ジャンプしたりできたら良いけれど　それも愛嬌　どうぞよろしく
It'd be nice if I could jump, but that's just part of my charm. Nice to meet you
でも今は関係ないんだよ　心響くリズムを辿れば
But it doesn't matter right now. If I follow the rhythm that resonates in my heart...
不思議な世界の続きのページで　また出会えたね　Destiny!
On the next page of this mysterious world, we met again. Destiny!
もしもし遅めのテンポも良いけど　今そんな場合じゃないわけじゃない
Hello, hello. A slow tempo is good too, but it's not like we don't have time for that
だけど大丈夫一息つけたのならば
But it's okay, if you've caught your breath...
さあ一二の三の合図で
Now, with the signal of one, two, three!
みんな行くよー！
Everyone, here we go!
一二の三！
One, two, three!
飛んでけハイ
Fly high
飛んでけフライ 大きく息を吸ったら
Fly away, take a deep breath
僕らのストーリーが今紡ぐ
Our story is unfolding now
もっともっと大きくね ボリュームはマックスね
Let's make it bigger and bigger, volume at max!
はじめまして こんにちは せーの ときのそらだよー！
Nice to meet you, hello! One, two, I'm Tokino Sora!
舞い踊る空 遠くへ響け
Dancing sky, let it echo far away
はちゃめちゃで任せ 不思議に煌めいた
Leave it to the chaos, it sparkled mysteriously
Dream Story やっぱ一人二人とも体感してたいの
Dream Story, after all, I want everyone to experience it
クラクラしちゃうくらい
To the point of getting dizzy
荒削り 最高じゃない
It's rough, but isn't it the best?
めでてテンション 高まってテンション
Celebrate the tension, rising tension
ワクワク警報は鳴り止まない
The excitement alarm won't stop ringing
めでてテンション 高まってテンション
Celebrate the tension, rising tension
誰も止められないわ
No one can stop it!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
High! High! High! High!
みんなコメント！
Everyone, leave comments!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
High! High! High! High!
最後はこのライブで行くよ！
Lastly, let's go with this live!
飛んでけフライ 大きく息を吸ったら
Fly away, take a deep breath
僕らのストーリーが今溢れ出すよ
Our story is overflowing now
もっともっと大きくね 最初が肝心なんです
Make it bigger and bigger, the beginning is crucial
これからもさあよろしくね せーの ホロライブだよ！
From now on, please treat me well! One, two, it's Hololive!
最速でフライ 空へ届け
Fly at top speed, reach for the sky
ドキドキで想定外に広がった
Heart pounding, it expanded unexpectedly
Dream Story やっぱ一人二人とも目を離さないでほしいの
Dream Story, after all, I want everyone to keep their eyes on us
まばたきもしてらんない
Can't even blink
あぁ、ほらね 最高でしょ
Ah, see, it's the best, right?
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんな見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for watching!
楽しかった！
That was fun!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
これからもよろしくお願いします！
Please keep supporting us!
はい、というわけで Dream☆Story を歌わせてもらいましたー！
Yes, so we just performed 'Dream☆Story'!
イエーイ！ やったー！
Yay! We did it!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
難しかったー。難しかった。
That was hard. It was difficult.
天を仰いだ。ごめん、ごめん。
I was looking up at the sky. Sorry, sorry.
でも楽しかった。
But it was fun.
よかったー。
I'm glad.
本当に。実はさ、
Truly. Actually,
ここのメンバーってさ、みんなアルバムを出してるんだよね。
all the members here have released an album.
そうなんです！ そうなんです。
That's right! We have.
なんとアルバム組じゃないですか。
We're the 'album group', aren't we?
そう、アルバムといえばなんですけど。
Yes, and speaking of albums...
今度？ 何？ 何？
Next? What is it? What?
実はお。私、ときのそら。
Actually... I, Tokino Sora...
ときのそら 3rd Album 『Re:Play』 2021年11月リリース決定！！
Tokino Sora 3rd Album 'Re:Play' Set for release in Nov 2021!!
ドン！
Bam!
えー、3rdアルバム『Re:Play』カバーアルバムをですね、
My 3rd album 'Re:Play', a cover album,
2021年11月にリリース決定しております！
is set to be released in November 2021!
おめでとー！ おめでとー！
Congratulations! Congratulations!
すみませんなんか、はい。というわけで戻していただいて大丈夫です。
Sorry about that. Yes. You can take the graphic down now.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
はい、というわけで。まあ皆さん、詳細まで全然わかんないんですけど、
Yes, so... well everyone, I don't have all the details yet,
ぜひ待っててくれると嬉しいです。
but I'd be happy if you look forward to it.
ねー。そうだ、これからね、2人はライブも...
Right. Oh, that's right, you two have a live coming up...
あ、そうなんです。我々はあります、あります。
Ah, that's right. We do, we do.
あるよねー。
You do, right?
いやみんなね、今回呼んだのはね、
Well, the reason I invited everyone this time is because,
あのやっぱりみんなたくさんアルバム出してて、歌が好きだっていう子たちが
after all, everyone has released many albums and I thought a group of people
集まってるかなと思って、そのメンバーで歌いたかったんです。
who love singing had gathered, so I wanted to sing with these members.
好きです。
I love you guys.
やったー！ ありがとうそらちゃん。
Yay! Thank you Sora-chan.
そらちゃんがさ、このメンバーを誘ってくれて、それで今日実現して、
Sora-chan invited these members, and that's why today happened.
なんか本当にもう、尊い気分。
I feel really blessed.
尊いって言われた。嬉しい。
She said 'blessed'. I'm happy.
嬉しいよ、ありがとう。
I'm so happy, thank you.
何て言うの、私グループも作ったんですよ。これからね。
What should I say, I even made a group. From now on.
これから末永く、
For a long time to come,
よろしくおねがいします。
let's do our best together.
いろんなことしていきましょう。いこう。一緒にしていこう。恐縮です。
Let's do various things. Let's go. Let's do it together. I'm humbled.
そうなんです。そういう意味も込めてね、これからね、いっぱね、みんなでね、
That's right. With that in mind, I thought it would be great if we all
仲良くしていったらいいんじゃないかなって思って、
got along well from now on,
そのきっかけになればいいなと思って、今日は呼びました。
and I invited you today hoping this would be the start of that.
うれしー、うれしー。
I'm so happy, so happy.
縄跳び。嬉しすぎて縄跳び。二重跳び。縄跳びしてるのかな。
Jump rope. I'm so happy I'm jump roping. Double unders. Is she jump roping?
はい、というわけでね。本当に素敵な3人が誘った子がみんな来てくれるって、
Yes, so... I think it's really a miracle that all three wonderful people
本当に奇跡だと思ってるから。本当にね、うれしいなって思います。
I invited actually came. I'm really, really happy.
本当にありがとう。
Thank you so much.
いつでも呼んで。いつでも呼んで。いつでもライブしよう。
Call us anytime. Call us anytime. Let's do a live anytime.
じゃあ明日で。明日はちょっと... スケジュールが。
Then tomorrow. Tomorrow is a bit... My schedule is...
いつでもいいって言ったじゃん！
You said anytime!
まあそんな風にね、言い合えるくらい私たち今仲いいので、
Well, we're close enough now to joke around like that,
ぜひぜひ皆さんもね、3人のチャンネルにも遊びに行ってほしいなって思います。
so I really hope everyone visits their three channels as well.
はい、というわけで。今日は本当にありがとうございましたー！
Yes, so... thank you so much for today!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございます！
なんでもないよ！
It's nothing!
５年目も止まらねーぞで！
We won't stop in the 5th year either!
あ、うん！
Ah, yeah!
５年目も止まらねーぞー！
We won't stop in the 5th year either!
お、見てるよ！
Oh, we're watching!
見、見、見てるかな？
I wonder if we're watching?
まだこれからそらちゃんのステージが...
Sora-chan's stage is still...
見てるよ、まだあるからな！
We're watching, there's still more!
もう一人ぼっちになっちゃうのかと思って...
I thought I'd be all alone already...
いるから、いるからね！
We're here, we're here!
いるからね、頑張ってね！
We're here, do your best!
見てるよ、見張ってるよ！
We're watching, keeping an eye on you!
見張ってるのは怖いけど...
Watching me is scary, but...
わかった！
I understand!
それでは一旦...
Well then, for now...
ステージに立つのはここで３人は最後ということで、ありがとうございました！
This is the last time the three of you will be on stage, so thank you very much!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
頑張ってね！頑張る！
Do your best! I will!
しゅっしゅっぱっぱー、しゅっしゅっぱっぱー
Shu shu pa pa, shu shu pa pa
しゅしゅでしゃなー
Shu shu de shana
急げ急げ、しゅっしゅっしゅー
Hurry, hurry, shu shu shu
お水飲みます
I'll drink some water
それでは歌います。
Well then, I will sing.
ここからは２曲連続で歌っていこうと思うので、ぜひ皆さん聴いてください。
From here, I'm going to sing two songs in a row, so please listen to them.
それでは、どうぞ。
Here we go.
沈むように溶けてゆくように
Sinking in, as if melting away
二人だけの空が広がる夜に
Into the night where a sky for only the two of us spreads out
「さよなら」だけだった、その一言ですべてが分かった
"Goodbye" was all it took, that one word made me understand everything
日が沈み出した空と君の姿
The sky where the sun began to set and your figure
フェンス越しに重なっていた
Overlapping across the fence
初めて会った日から僕の心のすべてを奪った
From the day we first met, you stole all of my heart
どこか儚い空気を纏う君は
You, wearing a somewhat ephemeral atmosphere
寂しい目をしていたんだ
Had lonely eyes
いつだってチックタックと鳴る世界で何度だってさ
In this world that always goes tick-tock, time and time again
触れる心無い言葉うるさい声に涙が零れそうでも
Even if tears are about to fall at the heartless words and noisy voices
ありきたりな喜びきっと二人なら見つけられる
An ordinary joy, I'm sure we can find it if we're together
騒がしい日々に笑えない君に
To you who cannot smile in these noisy days
思いつく限り眩しい明日を
A tomorrow as bright as I can imagine
明けない夜に落ちてゆく前に
Before falling into a night that never ends
僕の手を掴んでほら
Take my hand, look
忘れてしまいたくて閉じ込めた日々も
Even the days I locked away because I wanted to forget them
抱きしめた温もりで溶かすから
I'll melt them with the warmth of my embrace
怖くないよいつか日が昇るまで二人でいよう
It's not scary, let's be together until the sun rises someday
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
君にしか見えない何かを見つめる君が嫌いだ
I hate the you who gazes at something only you can see
見惚れているかのような恋するようなその顔が嫌いだ
I hate that face of yours, as if you're enchanted, as if you're in love
信じてたいけど信じれないこと、そんなのどうしたってきっと
Things I want to believe but can't, no matter what, surely
これからだっていくつもあってその度怒って泣いてくれる
There will be many more of those from now on, and each time you'll get angry and cry for me
それでもきっといつかはきっと僕らはきっと分かり合えるさ信じてるよ
Even so, surely someday, we'll surely be able to understand each other, I believe in us
もう嫌だって疲れたんだってがむしゃらに差し伸べる僕の手を振り払う君
You shake off my hand that I desperately reach out, saying you've had enough, that you're tired
もう嫌だって疲れたよなんて本当は僕も言いたいんだ
I want to say I've had enough, that I'm tired too, to be honest
あぁほらまたチックタックと鳴る世界で何度だってさ
Ah, look, in this world that goes tick-tock again, time and time again
君のために用意した言葉ももう届かない
The words I prepared for you no longer reach you
「終わりにしたい」だなんてさ、釣られて言葉にした時
When I said "I want to end this," lured by your words
君は初めて笑った
You smiled for the first time
騒がしい日々に笑えなくなっていた僕の目に映る君は綺麗だ
To my eyes that had become unable to smile in these noisy days, you look beautiful
明けない夜に零れた涙も君の笑顔に...
The tears that spilled in the night that never ends, into your smile...
…寄り添って溶けてゆく　あー
...snuggling and melting away, ahh
変わらない日々に泣いていた僕を
I was crying in the unchanging days
君は優しく終りへと誘う
And you gently invite me to the end
沈むように溶けてゆくように
As if sinking, as if melting away
染み付いた霧が晴れる
The ingrained mist clears up
忘れてしまいたくて閉じ込めた日々に
In the days I shut away wanting to forget
差し伸べてくれた君の手を取る
I take your hand that you reached out to me
涼しい風が空を泳ぐように今吹き抜けてゆく
A cool breeze blows through now as if swimming in the sky
繋いだ手を離さないでよ
Don't let go of our joined hands
二人今、夜に駆け出していく
The two of us are now racing out into the night
アンドロイドガール
Android Girl
もう一回、一生分の作りましょう
Let's make a lifetime's worth once more
君とのマッチアップの過程
The process of matching up with you
構ってもらって足りないの
I can't get enough of your attention
歌え、思い出染みた執奏のスタイル
Sing, the style of persistent performance stained with memories
カラフルカラフル傷つけては
Colorful, colorful, hurting each other
もうしないって嘘で仲直りごっこだ
Playing at making up with "won't do it again" lies
勘違いの騙し合い
Mutual deception of misunderstandings
目を見ればすぐにわかるって馬鹿みたい
Saying you'll know just by looking in my eyes is like a fool
妄想に耽って言うほど
As much as you say while indulging in delusions
この愛は腐ってるんだよ
This love is rotten
早く、気付いてんだよ
Quickly, I've noticed
アンドロイドガール、可笑しくなっちゃった
Android Girl, I've gone crazy
僕だけのものになった君は誰なの
Who are you who became mine alone?
ずっと、ずっと信じてきたのにね
Even though I believed for so, so long
アンドロイドガール、思いはなんだっけ
Android Girl, what were my thoughts again?
君とのキスが痛くて息を閉じたの
The kiss with you was so painful I stopped breathing
ずっと、ずっと何の愛を再起動したって
No matter how many times I reboot what kind of love
ちょっとだって代われやしないよ
Not even a little bit can be replaced
ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi!
あー可愛いね、どうしたくないよ
Ah, you're cute, I don't want to do anything about it
もう疲れた、ドキドキさせるお世辞のリサイズ
I'm tired already, resizing the flattery that makes my heart race
ウザい、ウザいの並行罪
Annoying, annoying parallel crimes
独占性の顔わからなくなったよ
I've lost sight of the face of exclusivity
エンドロールはまだですか
Are the end credits not here yet?
どこにいても一緒だなんてマジで痛い
Saying we're together wherever we are is seriously painful
感傷に浸っていいかな
Is it okay to soak in sentimentality?
あの頃を願っていいかな
Is it okay to wish for those days?
ありか、なしか、教えてよ
Is it a yes or a no, tell me
アンドロイドガール、可笑しくなっちゃった
Android Girl, I've gone crazy
君だけのものになった僕が好きなの
Do you like me who became yours alone?
ずっと、ずっと騙してきたんだね
You've been deceiving me for so, so long, haven't you?
アンドロイドガール、思いはなんだっけ
Android Girl, what were my thoughts again?
錆びついた腕で何度も僕を求めた
You sought me many times with rusted arms
ずっと、ずっと何の愛を再起動したって
No matter how many times I reboot what kind of love
ちょっとだって代われやしないよ
Not even a little bit can be replaced
アンドロイドガール、可笑しくなっちゃった
Android Girl, I've gone crazy
僕だけのものになった君は誰なの
Who are you who became mine alone?
ずっと、ずっと信じてきたのにね
Even though I believed for so, so long
アンドロイドガール、思いはなんだっけ
Android Girl, what were my thoughts again?
君とのキスが痛くて息を閉じたの
The kiss with you was so painful I stopped breathing
ずっと、ずっと
Always, always
わがままが離れない
Selfishness won't leave
君だけは許さない
I won't forgive only you
アンドロイドガール、可笑しくなっちゃった
Android Girl, I've gone crazy
君だけのものになった僕が好きなの
Do you like me who became yours alone?
ずっと、ずっと騙してきたんだね
You've been deceiving me for so, so long, haven't you?
アンドロイドガール、思いはなんだっけ
Android Girl, what were my thoughts again?
錆びついた腕で何度も僕を求めた
You sought me many times with rusted arms
ずっと、ずっと何の愛を再起動したって
No matter how many times I reboot what kind of love
ちょっとだって代われやしないよ
Not even a little bit can be replaced
何の愛を再起動したって
No matter what kind of love I reboot
ちょっとだって代われやしないよ
Not even a little bit can be replaced
はい！というわけで2曲連続歌わせていただきました。
Yes! And so, I sang two songs in a row.
えー、どちらも生で歌うのは初めてで、めちゃくちゃ緊張してたんですけど、いかがだったでしょうか？
Uh, it was my first time singing both of them live, so I was super nervous, but how was it?
今日はね、えっと、今は...
Today, well, right now...
今、今までよりも、
Right now, more than ever before,
すごく、なんか、5年目に入るということで、
Entering my fifth year feels...
なんか、いつもと違う緊張感があったかなと思うんですけど、
...like a different kind of tension than usual.
そんな時にね、
At a time like that,
3人に助けてもらって、
I was helped by those three,
すごくすごく、なんか自分の中で、
and within myself, there were many...
ま、悔しいところもいっぱい、いっぱいあるんですけど、
...frustrating moments, lots and lots of them,
とっても楽しい4周年ライブになったと思います。
but I think it's been a very fun 4th-anniversary live.
本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you all so much.
えー、5年ということでね、
Five years, you know?
これから5年目に入っていく、すごい、切りのいい数ではあるんですけども、
Entering the 5th year is a significant milestone.
まだまだ私にとっては、もう、あっという間に過ぎた時期でしたし、
But for me, the time has passed in the blink of an eye.
もっともっとみんなと、頑張っていきたいなと思っていますし、
I want to work harder and harder with everyone,
これからもみんなと、ずっとずっと歩いていきたいなって私思ってます。
and I want to keep walking with you all, forever and ever.
これからも私達についてきてくれますかー！？
Will you keep following us from now on as well!?
これからもどうぞよろしくお願いします。
I look forward to your continued support.
えー、みんな私の緊張伝わっちゃってたかな？
Um, did my nervousness reach all of you?
なんか緊張してても、楽しめればいいかなと思って、
I thought it was okay to just enjoy it even if I was nervous.
まあ始まる前はね、緊張しすぎて調子が調子が、って久々に言ってたんですけど、
Before starting, I kept saying I was too nervous, for the first time in a while.
ま、始まっちゃうとね、なんてことないなって。
But once it started, it was nothing.
こんなにたくさんの人が待っててくれるんだったら、
Since so many people were waiting for me,
私頑張れるなって思えましたし、
I felt like I could do my best.
やっぱね、一緒に歌うっていうのがとっても楽しかったです。
And singing together was just so much fun.
でも最後はさ、やっぱりさ、止まんじゃねぇぞ、止まらねぇぞ、ということでね、
But for the end, don't stop, we won't stop, right?
最後、私の、お誕生日に、ちょっと出した曲でね、
The last song is one I released on my birthday.
なんかすごいいっぱい「ヌンヌン」って言う曲なんですけども、
It's a song where we say "Nun Nun" a lot.
それをみんなで言っていこうかなと思います。
I want everyone to say it with me.
私が歌うんだけど、みんなにヌンヌンって言って欲しい。
I'll be singing, but I want everyone to say "Nun Nun".
練習だよ！
Let's practice!
ヌンヌンヌンヌンヌン ヌンヌンヌンヌンヌン！
Nun nun nun nun nun nun nun nun nun nun!
はい！
Alright!
言えたかな？あ、みんなヌンヌン言ってくれてますね。
Could you say it? Ah, everyone is saying "Nun Nun".
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
というわけで最後はこの曲で締めたいと思います。
So, I'd like to end with this song.
空ハレ！
KumoHurray!
ヌンヌンヌンヌンヌン ヌンヌンヌンヌンヌン
Nun nun nun nun nun nun nun nun nun nun
空ハレ進めどーしかー！！
Go forth, KumoHurray!!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ふわふわとリズム合わせて 踏み出す一歩どこまでも
Fluffy rhythms in sync, taking a step wherever we go
羽ばたいていけそう
I feel like I could just take flight
さあ ドキドキ ワクワク
Now, heart-pounding and exciting
胸が高鳴るよ この想いはもう 止まらない
My chest is thumping, these feelings won't stop anymore
みんな元気にいこうよ
Let's all go with energy
大きな声出して叫ぼう
Let's shout out with a loud voice
ハイ！ (イェーイ！)
High! (Yeah!)
空が明るくなっていく 眩しさ 君の心は
The sky is brightening with radiance, and your heart
曇り空 晴れ渡って虹をかけるよ
The cloudy sky will clear and a rainbow will form
胸を張って今を 進もう
Stand tall and move forward now
星のように輝いて
Shining like a star
いくよ！ハイ！
Here we go! High!
ヌンヌン！
Nun nun!
呼吸を合わせて 気持ち呼んでこ
Breathe in sync, calling forth our feelings
好奇心もシェア出来たらいいよね
It'd be nice if we could share our curiosity too
そっ 適当に
Well, just moderately
嘘だよ
Just kidding
些細な会話で 私たちは今 分かり合う
Through trivial talk, we understand each other now
超えていこう あのときの空よりも
Let's go beyond even that Tokino Sora
もっと遠くまで ハイ！ (イェーイ！)
Even further, High! (Yeah!)
みんな置いていかせないからね
I won't let anyone be left behind
さあ 止まらないよ
Now, we won't stop
もっと空に登るののののいで
Climbing higher into the sky
歩いてとととのの
Walking along
ゆっくりでも道はできる 夢の色描いて
A path will form even if slow, painting the colors of dreams
まさか5年間も、5年目に入れると思ってなかったので、
I never thought I'd make it to five years, let alone the fifth year,
本当に本当に嬉しいです。今日はありがとうございました！
so I'm really, really happy. Thank you so much for today!
見上げた気分も ちょっと目線を変えたなら
Even if you're looking up, if you change your perspective a bit...
ほら 心晴れ晴れ
See, your heart clears up
誇らしく 踊れるかもよ
Maybe you can dance proudly
一人じゃないよ
You're not alone
不安になったらここに来ればいいよ
If you get anxious, you can just come here
イェイ！
Yeah!
私はずっと待っているからね
Because I'll be waiting for you forever
負けてもいい頑張ってきたこと誇らしく
It's okay to lose, be proud of how hard you've worked
胸を張って 笑顔で行こう
Hold your head high and go with a smile
星のように輝いて
Shining like a star
最後みんな！
Everyone, for the last time!
行くよ！
Let's go!
ヌンヌンヌンヌンヌンヌンヌン
Nun nun nun nun nun nun nun
はい！
Yes!
ヌンヌンヌンヌンヌン
Nun nun nun nun nun
前に進め！
Move forward!
みんな、今日はありがとうございました！
Everyone, thank you so much for today!
バイバーーイ！
Bye-bye!
最後に、ときのそらからの告知タイムです！
Finally, it's announcement time from Tokino Sora!
ときのそら4周年記念グッズ、発売決定！
Tokino Sora 4th Anniversary Goods, release decided!
BIGメガネ置きアクリルスタンドと、活動四周年記念ピンバッジを作りました。
I made a BIG glasses-holding acrylic stand and a 4th anniversary activity pin badge.
詳細はこちら！
Details are here!
イラストはおるだん先生です。
The illustration is by Ordan-sensei.
私に好きなメガネをかけて楽しんでね。
Please enjoy putting your favorite glasses on me.
ピンバッジはこちら。
The pin badge is here.
あん肝デザインの素敵なピンバッジです。
It's a wonderful pin badge with an Ankimo design.
22時から発売開始。
Sales start at 22:00.
ぜひ皆さん購入してね。
Everyone, please buy them.
そして、もう今日のお昼には発表されているのですが、
And, it was already announced this afternoon, but...
私ときのそらのねんどろいどが受注開始しています！
...my, Tokino Sora's, Nendoroid pre-orders have started!
笑顔やジト目、あん肝もついてきます！
It comes with a smiling face, a glaring face, and even Ankimo!
さらに懐かしの猫耳や猫手があったり、マイク持ち手もあるので、
Furthermore, there are nostalgic cat ears and cat paws, and also a microphone-holding hand...
この機会を逃すと手に入らないよ。
...so if you miss this chance, you won't be able to get it.
ぜひみんな予約してね。
Everyone, please pre-order.
合わせて、さっきも告知した通り、カバーアルバムも現在制作中です。
Also, as announced earlier, a cover album is currently in production.
タイトルは『Re:Play』。
The title is "Re:Play".
2021年11月リリース決定！！
Confirmed for release in November 2021!!
収録曲などは今後の情報をお待ちください。
Please look forward to future information such as the tracklist.
さらに、なんと、なんと、このあと9月8日水曜日0時より、
Furthermore, believe it or not, from 0:00 on Wednesday, September 8th...
4周年を記念して、過去のアルバムの未配信楽曲を配信にてリリースします！
...to commemorate the 4th anniversary, we will release previously unreleased songs from past albums on streaming services!
『Dreaming!』の初回盤特典シークレットトラックで収録された『シーソーゲーム』、
"Seesaw Game" recorded as a secret track in the "Dreaming!" first press limited edition bonus,
『パラレルタイム』の初回限定盤特典に収録された『コトバカゼ』、『Wonderland』、『Step and Go!』のアコースティックバージョン、
acoustic versions of "Kotobakaze", "Wonderland", and "Step and Go!" recorded in the "Parallel Time" first press limited edition bonus,
私のチャンネルで投稿した『キ、泣いちゃいそうだ』のアコースティック音源の全5曲です！
and the acoustic sound source of "Ki, Naichaisou da" posted on my channel, making a total of 5 songs!
告知は以上だよ。
That's all for the announcements.
今日は配信見に来てくれて、ありがとーーー！
Thank you for coming to watch the stream today!